(Howard:)that we're gonna be living here
the next few months.
(Bernadette:)But we have jobs.
We can't babysit her 24 hours a day.
(Howard:)Well, what if we use
our vacation time?
(Bernadette:)I wanted to go to Hawaii, not Hell.
(Howard:)I don't know what else we can do.
(Bernadette:)Howie, I love you, and as your wife,
your mother is every bit
(Bernadette:)as much my problem
as she is yours, so...
(Bernadette:)...I want a divorce.
(Mrs Hofstadter(on webcam):)Hello, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Hi, Mom.
(Leonard:)I have some exciting news.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)I'm listening.
(Leonard:)Before I tell you,
will you promise to try
(Leonard:)and be happy for me and keep
any concerns you have to yourself?
(Howard:)No.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)Let me save you all
of your hemming and hawing.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)Sheldon already told me
that you and Penny are engaged.
(Leonard:)I hate that you talk to him
more than you talk to me.